I know it all
我都知道了
Do they really trust you?
他们真的信任你了吗
That's good
那就好
can say that
也算是
My prison meals these days have not been in vain.
我这几天的牢饭没白吃
I feel wronged to you
委屈你了
Not wronged
不委屈
I found it
我发现了
I am now
我现在啊
Just professional cannon fodder
就是职业炮灰
but
不过
I'm really happy this time
这次我是真高兴
As long as you can successfully land
只要你能成功上岸
It's worth it even if I'm broken to pieces
就算我粉身碎骨也值得
Zicheng
子诚
Thank you
谢谢你
Why are you so polite to me?
你跟我这么客气干嘛呀
Have we been there for a long time?
我们是不是已经很久
nothing like now
没有像现在这样
Stay together
待在一起了
yes
是
but
不过
This thing
这事情啊
Getting better little by little
一点一点在变好
Later
以后啊
the time we spend together
我们待在一起的时间
there will be many
会有很多的
But
可是
But I'm leaving Jinhai
可是我要离开津海了
where to
去哪儿
As soon as Zhou Zhe transferred me,
周哲一把我调到
The operating company of Agent Game
特工游戏的运营公司
Make me the game director
让我当游戏主管
so suddenly
这么突然
If you want to get his evidence
如果想要拿到他的证据
this is an opportunity
这是一个机会
no
不行
you can't go
你不能去
Too dangerous
太危险了
Didn’t you just say that?
你刚刚不也说了吗
this could be me
这可能是我
Last chance to go ashore
最后上岸的机会了
It's worth it to be broken into pieces
粉身碎骨都值得
That
那
Have you thought it through?
你想清楚了吗
Think it through
想清楚了
That
那
will you go with me
你会跟我一起去吗
I
我
Do you need me to go with you?
你需要我陪你一起去吗
I'm teasing you
我逗你的
Are you kidding me?
跟你开玩笑呢
this is myself
这是我自己
Things that need to be faced
需要去面对的事情
It has nothing to do with you
跟你没什么关系
I go
我去
Yao Yao
姚瑶
What about you?
你这个人呢
When you lie
一撒谎的时候
I just like to pick my fingernails
就喜欢抠自己的手指甲
You must pay attention to this
这个你一定要注意
any detail
任何一个细节
will betray you
都会出卖你
You won't do it for no reason
你不会无缘无故
Tell me to accompany you
跟我说让我陪你
If we go together
一起去的这种话
If I guess correctly
如果我没猜错的话
i should be you
我应该是你
Go back as a bargaining chip
回去的筹码吧
Can they offer such conditions?
他们能开出这样的条件
Just show
就说明
They don't fully trust you yet
他们还没有完全信任你
I went
我去了
Can help you gain their trust
能帮你获取他们的信任
But you know it
可是你明知道
this is a trap
这是一个陷阱
If you go there, you'll be free to eat mermaid meat.
去了就是任人鱼肉
If I don't go
如果我要是不去
The man who lets people eat meat
那个任人鱼肉的人
it's you
就是你
Yewu has already agreed
夜雾已经答应了
my request
我的要求
After getting the HY106 data
拿到HY106数据以后
Arrange for me and Boss Zhang
安排我和张老板
leave together
一起离开
leave
离开
I thought
我以为
You just go through Boss Zhang
你只是通过张老板
Come and investigate the secrets hidden in Jinhai
来调查隐藏在津海的
spy network
间谍网络
why do you want to leave
你为什么要离开
The night fog is now
夜雾现在已经
Starting to doubt me
开始怀疑我了
let me risk
让我冒险
Take this experimental data
拿这个实验数据
obviously not them
显然不是他们
best choice
最优的选择
I do not have either
我也没有
One hundred percent sure
百分之百的把握
But they still let me do it
但是他们还是让我做了
Then they still have a backup plan
那他们还有后手
In the hands of Boss Zhang
张老板手里边
One more trump card
还有一张王牌
Just inside the Bio Group
就在生物集团内部
His actions are more reliable
他的行动更可靠
so let you go
所以让你去
It's their usual trick
是他们的一贯伎俩
The plank road was repaired in the open, but Chencang was buried in the dark
明修栈道 暗度陈仓
That's right
没错
Thanks
谢谢
You go to Yewu to work as an undercover agent
你去夜雾做卧底
It's impossible
是不可能的事
why
为什么呀
You are a national security officer
你是国安人员
How can they trust you?
他们怎么可能信任你呢
You are the biggest to them
你对他们最大的
Utilization value
利用价值
That means you stay in the National Security Bureau
就是你留在国安局
once you leave
一旦你离开了
You have no value anymore
你就没有任何价值了
How could they take you in?
他们怎么会收留你呢
It's too risky for you to do this
你这样做也太冒险了
you have a point
你说得有道理
But for the mission
但是为了任务
i must take risk
我必须冒险
No, I have to talk to him.
不行 我得跟他说说去
Don't make trouble for others
你别给人家添乱了
Can you believe me once?
你能不能相信我一次啊
I can't die
我死不了
Look, are you sad now?
你瞧你现在 你丧不丧
what is this
这是什么呀
These were all given by Zicheng
这些都是子诚给的
Look like
像不像
unlike
不像
these things
这些东西
Just help me keep it safe first.
你就帮我先保管着吧
OK
行
I'm waiting for you to come back
我等你回来
Give it back to you
再还给你
Thank you, Officer Wu
谢谢吴警官
You're welcome
不客气
Section Chief Gao
高科长
I don't even remember
我都不记得
Last time I came to the beach
上一次来海边
when is it
是什么时候了
Often things around us
往往身边的事
Most easily ignored
最容易忽略了
you have to do me a favor
你得帮我一个忙
What are you busy with?
什么忙
i need one
我需要一份
The latest HY106 data
最新的HY106的数据
Ye Wu asked you to do it
夜雾让你做的
Finish this time
做完这一次
I'm ready to leave
我就准备离开
where to
去哪儿
have no idea
不知道
I'm leaving anyway
反正就要离开了
I also decided
我也决定了
I'm going with Yao Yao
我和姚瑶一起走
Zicheng
子诚
You don't have to go with me
你没有必要跟我一起去
you don't want
你不希望
Shall I go with you?
我和你一起去吗
this is too dangerous
这太危险了
Isn't it dangerous for you to go?
你去就不危险了吗
Do not worry
放心吧
I am now a professional cannon fodder
我现在是职业炮灰
if i don't leave
如果我不走
They won't trust you either
他们也不会信任你
Is it right
对吗
So comfortable
真舒服啊
do you remember
你还记得吗
When we were kids
我们小时候
This is my favorite time to go swimming
最喜欢这个时候去游泳
I can also go into the water now
我现在也能下水啊
Do you really want to do it?
你真的要下
Leave him
别管他
He's like that
他就那样
Do whatever comes to mind
想到什么就做什么
Brother Tianyang
天阳哥
really want him
真的要让他
come with me
跟我一起去吗
if he doesn't go
如果他不去
All efforts are wasted
一切都前功尽弃了
really dangerous
真的很危险
when necessary
必要的时候
It requires sacrifice
是需要牺牲的
But that's your brother
但那是你弟弟
this is the struggle
这就是斗争
Now that you have chosen to join
既然选择了加入
That requires wisdom and courage
那就需要智慧和勇气
to fight
去战斗
rather than shrinking back
而不是退缩
Do not worry
放心吧
Someone will be responsible for his safety
他的安全会有人负责的
come
来呀
Come on, Gao Tianyang
来呀 高天阳
Coming
来啦
Come down and play for a while
下来玩会儿
It’s time to eat
吃饭了啊
It’s time to eat, it’s time to eat
吃饭了 吃饭了
No rest at noon
中午不休息啊
Is it noon?
中午了吗
It's almost half past twelve
快十二点半了都
You said you, old comrade
你说你这老同志
We can’t just focus on construction.
也不能光顾着搞建设啊
You also have to pay attention to your health
也得注意身体
There is another meeting in the afternoon
下午还有个会呢
No meal at noon
中午不吃饭啦
eat
吃
Xiao Liu went to buy it
小刘去买去了
Fine
行吧
Then I won't bother you
那我就不打扰
The leader is working
领导工作了
I'll call my brother back tonight
晚上我叫哥回来
Let's have a meal together
咱们一块儿吃个饭
OK
好啊
Fortunately, I have nothing to do in the afternoon
正好我下午没什么事
What to eat
想吃什么
I'll go buy it in advance in the afternoon
我下午提前去买
Don't worry about it
不劳您操心
The two of us will do it for you
我们俩啊 给您做
I will honor and honor you well.
好好孝敬孝敬您
I feel like this attitude is not quite right.
感觉这个态度不太对呀
I thought you came to me
我还以为你来找我
Is there some bad news to announce?
是有什么噩耗要宣布
or
要不
Just come to borrow money from me
就是来跟我借钱
Why am I in your heart
我怎么在你心里
This image is so unbearable
这形象就这么不堪啊
Anyway, if you
反正吧 您要是
If you really want to help me
实在是想接济我的话
Then I won’t refuse
那我也不推辞了
You boy, you
你这个小子 你
You two are Lao Huang's sons, right?
你俩是老黄的儿子吧
When I was a kid, I followed behind
小时候啊 跟在后面
It's so big now
现在都这么大了
Okay, it looks good.
行啊 有模有样的
When I said frying fish
我说煎鱼的时候
You have to watch it carefully
得看好了啊
Don't burn it, I tell you
别煎煳了 我告诉你
If you can do it, come
你要是行 你来
That's not okay
那可不行
Today we agreed that you two will do it
今儿说好了你们俩做
I eat ready-made
我吃现成的
brother
哥哥哥
Look at my fish
你看我这鱼
Isn't it a bit too much?
是不是炸得有点过呀
uncle
舅舅
Come, come, come and see
来来 快 快来看
Zicheng’s fried fish is so awesome
这子诚炸的鱼太牛了
Come on come on
快来 快来
Why is it so delicious?
咋就这么大味啊
It won’t burn after it’s fried.
炸 是不煳了呀
What did I just say?
我刚才怎么说来着
Mixed up like this
煳成这样
How can we still eat it, you say?
还怎么吃啊 你说
never mind
算了
The pan is sticky
粘锅了
We can go out to eat
咱们出去吃得了
Go out to eat
出去吃啊
What time is it?
都几点了
There are queues everywhere now
现在哪儿哪儿都排队
Wait until he doesn't starve to death
等他不得饿死啊
Don't, don't, don't worry
别别别 别着急
I think of a way
我想办法
Think of a way, think of a way
想办法 想办法
Isn’t this dish a good cut?
这菜切得不是不错吗
Then eat hot pot instead and that's it.
那改吃火锅就完了嘛
high high
高 高
come on! Come on
加油 加油
come on, come on, come on
加油 加油 加油
Gao Tianyang Gao Tianyang
高天阳 高天阳
Always the last one
永远得最后一名
How about it
怎么样
Accept or not
服不服
I said you didn't mean it
我说你们不是故意
Give me some water
放我水的吧
No, no, no
没没没
Not this time, really not this time
这次没有 这次真没有
The sword is not old yet
宝刀未老
Invincibility is so lonely
无敌就是这么让人寂寞
You are still a master
你还高手呢
Even I can't play it
连我都玩不过
He just has good hands
他就是手高
drink drink drink
喝酒 喝酒
Come, come, have a drink
来来来 喝酒
A cup of honor yellow
敬老黄一杯
do it again do it again do it again
再来一次 再来一次
One more round, come on, come on
再来一局 来来来
Uncle, let’s go first
舅舅 我们先走了啊
Slow down on the road
路上慢点
Go back and rest early
回去早点休息
What's going on? This is
这是怎么了这是
You also give Lao Huang a hug
你也和老黄拥抱一个
What's going on today?
今儿个是咋了
It's like a farewell ceremony
搞得跟告别仪式似的
This hug
这拥抱啊
It’s etiquette between normal people
是正常人之间的礼仪
Later
以后啊
We have to be normal too
咱们也得正常点
Okay, okay, you have many tricks
行行行 就你花样多
let's go
走吧 走吧
You go back
你回去吧
You go quickly
你快走吧
OK OK OK
行行行
I won’t send it to you anymore
我不送你们了啊
Take care of yourself
注意身体啊
Where are you going?
去哪儿啊
Go to Yao Yao's place
去姚瑶那儿
action tomorrow
明天的行动
Nothing can go wrong
不能出任何差错
Someone will be watching us
会有人监视我们
clear
明白
Came back so early
这么早就回来了
I've just finished eating
我刚吃完饭
What do you want to eat
你想吃什么
I'll do it for you
我给你做
No
不用了
when to act
什么时候行动
tomorrow
明天
so fast
这么快啊
I'm really reluctant to give up
我还真有点舍不得
I will leave with you
我会跟你一起离开
Mr. Yu and I have finished talking.
我跟余先生已经谈完了
Have you considered
你想好了吗
What
什么
After going abroad
出国以后
What do you want to do
你想干什么
what do you think i can do
你觉得我能做什么
be my partner
做我搭档
I don't want to be
我可不想成为
Another Xiao Yi
另外一个肖逸
Will not
不会的
you are so smart
你那么聪明
Yes
对呀
I can play the spy game
我可以玩特工游戏啊
I heard about that game
我听说那个游戏
Especially profitable
特别赚钱
you don't need to play games
你不需要玩游戏
you are already one
你已经是一个
Very good agent
很优秀的特工了
There will be many companies hiring you
会有很多公司雇用你
Do you think Ye Wu can take me in?
你说夜雾能收留我吗
Who knows
谁知道啦
Let’s talk about it after we get out.
等出去以后再说吧
You should pack your things first
你先收拾东西吧
Don't wait for me at home tomorrow
明天别在家等我了
Why
为什么
Tomorrow's action is an adventure
明天的行动是一次冒险
If I'm going to get caught
如果我要被抓了
Just escape by yourself
你就自己逃吧
you were caught
你被抓了
If I confess, I can be imprisoned for a few years less
供出我 可以少关几年
Pointless
没有意义
To me it's do or die
对我来讲不成功便成仁
no retreat
没有退路
Don't be too nice to me
不要对我太好
i will disappoint you
我会让你失望的
I didn't expect it
我就没期待
what can you give me
你能给我什么
That's good
那就好
can i ask a personal question
我能问一个私人问题吗
What
什么
do you have a family
你有家人吗
I only have myself
我只有我自己
This is the emotional bond we have in this business
干我们这行感情羁绊
Will mislead my judgment
会误导我的判断
Then why did you choose one?
那你为什么选择一条
Such a difficult road
这么艰难的路
Then why do you want to be a national security officer?
那你为什么要当国安
avoiding problem
逃避问题
Tell me first
你先说说看
let me think
让我想一想
Do you want to answer your question?
要不要回答你的问题
university graduate
大学毕业
Apply for national security
报考国安
Passed the training
培训通过
Then take up the job
然后上岗
It's that simple
就这么简单
I don't want to know
我可不想知道
Guoan recruitment process
国安招人的流程
What I'm asking is
我问的是
Why are you
你为什么
To be a national security officer
要当国安
My parents were in a fire
我爸妈在一场火灾中
died accidentally
意外死了
And that accident
而那次事故
that's because
就是因为
Caused by spies stealing secrets
间谍窃密造成的
I thought I was going to hear a
我还以为我会听到一个
How ambitious
多么有抱负
and pursuit story
和追求的故事
Unexpectedly, it was also hatred
没想到也是仇恨
This is not revenge
这不算什么复仇
The person who died is no longer there
去世的人不在了
but living people
但活着的人
I must protect
我必须要保护
I'm done
我说完了
Are you satisfied with my answer?
我这个回答你还满意吗
When I was young
我小时候
Maybe worse than you
可能比你还惨
little mute
小哑巴
Come this way
您这边来
Look at the children in our courtyard
你看咱们院里的孩子们
They're all down there
都在下面呢
little mute
小哑巴
Then I'll go and get busy first.
那我先去忙了啊
If you don’t cry or make trouble, you’re a fool
不哭不闹大傻瓜
cry
哭啊
little mute
小哑巴
Really annoying
真讨厌
Don't cry or make trouble
不哭不闹
know why
知道为什么
will i choose you
我会选中你吗
Because there is hatred in your eyes
因为你眼中有恨
like now
就像现在这样
Even in desperate situation
即使身处绝境
Still want to bite the enemy back?
还想反咬敌人一口啊
Although your eyes are good
你眼神虽好
but sometimes
但有时候
An act of overestimation
不自量力的举动
It will make you suffer
会让你吃亏的
Do you still hate them?
还恨他们吗
Remember this feeling
记住这种感觉吧
hatred
恨
Sometimes it makes people stronger
有时候让人更强大呀
don't ask me
不问我
will i take you somewhere
我会带你去哪里吗
where to
去哪儿
It's better than here now
都比现在这儿好
You will live here from now on
以后你就住在这里啊
Get along well with everyone
跟大家好好相处
What are you doing
你干嘛
release
松开
Okay, okay, okay
好了 好了 好了
let go
松手
Let go
放手啊
Excuting an order
执行命令
don't want
不要
Don't don't
不要 不要
Where are you taking her?
你们要带她去哪儿
accept punishment
接受惩罚
She needs to calm down and think carefully
她要静下来好好想想
Why did she lose?
她为什么会输的
Do you want to have a fight too?
你也想打一场吗
One is eliminated every week
每周都有一个被淘汰
new ones coming in
新的进来
Replace the one who was eliminated
顶替那个被淘汰的
I don't want to be eliminated
我不想被淘汰
I don't want to either
我也不想
I didn't know until later
后来我才知道
that place
那地方
It's a spy school, right?
算是个间谍学校吧
They recruit from all over
他们从各地招收
Children of school age
适龄儿童
Raised since childhood, systematic training
从小养大 系统培训
Then
然后
and then transported to various countries
再输送到各个国家
Become a real spy
成为真正的间谍
what you just said
你刚才说的
Is it training?
是训练吗
almost every week
几乎每周都有
People keep being sent away
不断有人被送走
Someone will disappear suddenly
有人会突然消失
Some people can't stand the torture
有人会受不了折磨
suicide
自杀
But soon
不过很快
There will be new children
又会有新的孩子
fill in
填补进来
cruel
残酷
indifferent
冷漠
ruthless
无情
Mission first
任务至上
through training one at a time
通过一次一次训练
Kill all normal emotions
消磨掉所有正常的情感
Leave only what is needed
只留下需要的
But it's okay
不过还好
I made at least one friend
我至少交到一个朋友
only friend
唯一的朋友
that boy
那个男孩
It's Ran Fei, right?
就是冉飞吧
So you are so sure
所以你那么确定
He won't betray me
他不会供出我
You believe it
你信了
No, Section Chief Gao
不会吧 高科长
Such a vulgar story
这么俗的故事
You believe it too
你也信
I just like clichéd stories
我就喜欢俗套的故事
Is there any follow-up?
还有后续吗
story without ending
没有结局的故事
That's the most perfect
才最完美啊
According to your story
按照你这个故事
I won't be
我不会是
Be the next one to be eliminated
下一个被淘汰的人吧
As long as one person is still valuable
只要一个人还有价值
won't be eliminated
就不会被淘汰
It seems I still have value
看来我还有价值
certainly
当然
So keep it
所以要保留住
own value
自己的价值
Don't do stupid things
别做傻事
You do it
你来吧
Look at me
看我的
what does it feel like
什么感觉
It's like a lifetime ago
恍如隔世
Zicheng
子诚
I think you should stay
我觉得你应该留下
Have you ever thought about it
你想过没有
If Brother Tianyang goes
如果天阳哥去了
You went too
你也去了
What about uncle?
那伯父怎么办
It’s not like I won’t come back if I go.
我去了也不是不回来了
But even I went
可是连我去了
Don't even know what to face
都不知道应该面对什么
What's more, it's you
更何况是你呢
so
所以啊
That makes it even more necessary for me to go
这样我就更得去了
I have to protect you
我得去保护你
Protect
保护
How do you protect me?
你怎么保护我啊
The two of us were alone there
我们两个人孤身在那儿
What we have to face is
要面对的是
entire espionage organization
整个间谍组织
You can't even protect yourself
你连你自己都保护不了
What are you doing to protect me?
你拿什么保护我啊
Huang Zicheng
黄子诚
you will always be like this
你永远都是这样
feel good about yourself
自我感觉良好
But you never know
可是你永远都不知道
after you pass
你过去之后
What dangers will you face?
将要面对的危险是什么
Yao Yao
姚瑶
It's not like I haven't experienced it before
我之前也不是没经历过
Wouldn't they take me too?
他们不也拿我
Nothing wrong?
没怎么样吗
I know you are comforting me
我知道你是在安慰我
But now that you've escaped
可是既然你已经脱身了
Just don't get involved anymore, okay?
就不要再卷进去了好吗
So I can't let you
所以我更不能让你
Go alone
只身前往啊
if you can
如果可以的话
someone i'd rather go to
我宁愿去的人
it's me
是我
It's all doomed
这一切都是注定的
Now things have developed like this
现在事情发展成这样
Brother Tianyang and I must leave
我跟天阳哥必须离开
But you are different
但是你不一样
You still have a home
你还有家
And uncle
还有伯父
You can still stay in Jinhai
你还可以继续留在津海
fulfill your dream
完成你的梦想
If you have a chance
如果有机会
we can meet again
我们还能再见
No but me
不是 可是我
Stop talking
你别说了
Listen to me this time
这次听我的
Just let me beg you, okay?
算我求你了 好吗
OK
好啦
the time we can stay together
我们能待在一起的时间
Running out
不多了
Don't waste this time anymore
就不要再浪费这些时间
in some unnecessary
在一些无谓的
Things are over
事情上面了
We've been together for so long
我们在一起这么久了
Not one yet
还没有一张
What about the official group photo?
正式的合照呢
Yes
对呀
But it's so late
可是这么晚了
No place to take pictures
没有地方拍照了
Not always
那可不一定
look
你看
Where are you going?
去哪儿啊
there
那儿
Zicheng
子诚
Where are you taking me?
你要带我去哪儿啊
let's get married
咱们结婚吧
Right here
就是这儿吧
What are you going to do?
就 你干嘛去呀
Come
来
Wait for me here
在这儿等我啊
this this
这个 这个
Am I wearing this?
我穿这个是不是
Very strange
特别奇怪啊
Not surprising at all
一点也不奇怪
very beautiful
很漂亮
real
真的
correct
对了
You just talked to them
你刚刚跟他们
What have you said?
都说什么了
I'll tell them
我就跟他们说
I want to be with me
我要和我
The one you love proposes
爱的人求婚
Full of lies
满嘴谎话
I really think so
我真是这么想的
look
你看
I even prepared the ring
我连戒指都准备了
Okay, stop making trouble
行了 你别闹了
Let's take a photo
我们就拍张照片
Just leave it as a souvenir
留个纪念就行了
Just the two of us
只要我们两个人
at this moment
此时此刻
It's enough to be together
能在一起就够了
bring it on
来吧
Look here, you two.
好 二位看这里啊
good very good
好好 非常好
good
好
Let's make out
来 亲热一点
Okay, one more
好 再来一张
good
不错
thank you
谢谢啊
I can't move this
这动不了了
You can't move either
你也动不了了
I can't do this anymore
我这也不行了
what happened
到底怎么回事啊
our firewall
我们的防火墙
being attacked
正在被攻击
The system has activated an emergency state
系统启动了应急状态
Turn off the Internet immediately
马上关掉网络
lead
领导
This is a malicious attack
这是有人恶意攻击
It should be reported to the security department immediately
应该马上上报安全部门
I'll report it immediately
我马上上报
You cut off the Internet immediately
你们立刻切断网络
yes
是
what happened
怎么回事
half an hour ago
半个小时前
Our network firewall
我们网络防火墙
Being maliciously attacked
被人恶意攻击了
Have you cut off the Internet?
切断网络了吗
cut off
切断了
Data will not be leaked for the time being
数据暂时不会外流
But there is already a problem with the intranet
但是内网已经出问题了
take us to see
带我们去看看
Good here
好 这边
Everyone here
各位 这边
This is a virus attack
这是被病毒攻击了
I need to find the source of the virus
我需要找到病毒的来源
Use my computer
用我的电脑吧
Please come this way
这边请吧
good
好
I suspect there is someone
我怀疑是有人
Hacked into our internal systems
黑入了我们的内部系统
Group’s core data
集团的核心数据
Where is it
在什么地方啊
in data center
在数据中心
data center
数据中心
Should we
我们是不是应该
Go to some core departments and check
去一些核心部门查一查
Enter data center maintenance
进入数据中心维护
Requires personal approval from the Vice President
需要副总的亲自批示
Mr. Huang went to a meeting
黄总开会去了
I've reported it to him
我已向他汇报过了
request assistance
要求协助
National security personnel inspection
国安人员检查
All right
好吧
follow me
跟我来
You lead the way
你带路
Gao Tianyang is just a cover
高天阳只是个幌子
attract everyone's attention
吸引所有人的注意力
He is the real big fish
他才是真正的大鱼啊
Taking advantage of Huang Zicheng
趁着黄子诚
When attacking a network
攻击网络的时候
The sample was taken away quietly
悄无声息地拿走了样本
This plan is perfect
这个计划很完美
need someone now
现在需要有人
Bring the sample back
把样本带回来
Isn’t it Boss Zhang?
不是张老板吗
She wants to deal with Gao Tianyang
她要对付高天阳
The risk is too great
风险太大
we want to find one
我们要找一个
Someone who even the National Security Bureau trusts
连国安都相信的人
Yao Yao
姚瑶